<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>YP-HOME</title><link>http://pengyangraul.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on YP-HOME</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="http://pengyangraul.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CV</title><link>http://pengyangraul.github.io/cv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://pengyangraul.github.io/cv/</guid><description>Contact info Link to heading Email: yang.peng@csun.edu Current Appointment Link to heading California State University, Northridge (Northridge, CA, USA)
Assistant Professor: Jan. 2020 – Present Previous Experiences Link to heading California Institute of Technology (Pasadena, CA, USA)
Sherman Fairchild Postdoctoral Fellow in Theoretical Physics: Sep. 2017 – Jan. 2020 Fachbereich Physik, Freie Universität Berlin (Berlin, Germany)
PhD in Theoretical Physics: Oct. 2013 – Aug. 2017 Fritz‑Haber‑Institut der Max‑Planck‑Gesellschaft (Berlin, Germany)</description></item><item><title>PUBLICATIONS</title><link>http://pengyangraul.github.io/publications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://pengyangraul.github.io/publications/</guid><description>My publications and citation information can be found at Google Scholar.
Yang Peng, Topological Space-Time Crystal, Phys. Rev. Lett. 128, 186802, 2022 Zihao Qi, Gil Refael, and Yang Peng, Universal nonadiabatic energy pumping in a quasiperiodically driven extended system, Phys. Rev. B 104, 224301, 2021 Youngjoon Choi, Hyunjin Kim, Cyprian Lewandowski, Yang Peng, Alex Thomson, Robert Polski, Yiran Zhang, Kenji Watanabe, Takashi Taniguchi, Jason Alicea and Stevan Nadj-Perge, Interaction-driven Band Flattening and Correlated Phases in Twisted Bilayer Graphene, Nature Physics 17, 1375–1381, 2021 Youngjoon Choi, Hyunjin Kim, Yang Peng, Alex Thomson, Cyprian Lewandowski, Robert Polski, Yiran Zhang, Harpreet Singh Arora, Kenji Watanabe, Takashi Taniguchi, Jason Alicea and Stevan Nadj-Perge, Correlation-driven topological phases in magic-angle twisted bilayer graphene, Nature 589, 536-541, 2021 Changnan Peng, Arbel Haim, Torsten Karzig, Yang Peng and Gil Refael, Floquet Majorana bound states in voltage-biased Planar Josephson Junctions, Phys.</description></item><item><title>Research</title><link>http://pengyangraul.github.io/research/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://pengyangraul.github.io/research/</guid><description> I&amp;rsquo;m currently interested in: Link to heading Topological phenomena in out-of-equilibrium quantum system Nonequilibrium quantum dynamics in general Interplay between symmetries and topology in quantum system 2D Morie materials</description></item><item><title>Teaching</title><link>http://pengyangraul.github.io/teaching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://pengyangraul.github.io/teaching/</guid><description> Teaching at CSUN Link to heading PHYS 490: Computer Applications in Physics, 2022 Fall PHYS 651: Quantum Mechanics II, 2022 Spring PHYS 650: Quantum Mechanics I, 2021 Fall PHYS 651: Quantum Mechanics II, 2021 Spring PHYS 585: Computational material theory, 2020 Fall Teaching Assistant at FU-Berlin Link to heading Theoretical Solid State Physics, Sommersemester 2017 Quantum Field Theory and Many Body Physics, Sommersemester 2016 Quantum Field Theory and Many Body Physics, Sommersemester 2015</description></item></channel></rss>